Manek you take all I medallion how do we
know he's not just want to sell them at
some pawn shop you don't
[Music]
that's robotic security panel only way
passage with the frequency harmonizer
Xhosa could I borrow Robotnik's up
frequency harmonized exten yeah uh right
all right just use it
Manek tell me you can get us on ever
well I was going to take them after over
Ikey but my Sofia was no time to be
spirits up right you not why can was it
amazed
[Music]
I'm only here because I was personally
invited by dr. Robotnik he and I are
excuse me excuse me excuse me um coming
through coming through calling her
[Music]
so for
holding
right you think my aerobicize our mini
Jameson in our luggage
luck yes another snooty diva joined the
resistance